Guide to the Jimmy De Sana Papers 1954-1997 (bulk 1977-1990) MSS.202
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Prints by theme
  - Subseries B: Events
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Head phones
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: PS 1
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: "Ronnie Cutrone's friend Walter…SoHo Saturdays"
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Interior with television
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Television Crew
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Man with monitor
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Gun shots
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: "Ray - o - gram"
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Foot inside shirt
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
  - Subseries C: Landscape
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Landscape
      Number of Items: 12
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
    - Title: (Box 6)
      Description: Altered Landscape
  - Subseries D: Paper Collage
    Box 7 is an oversized flat box.
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Description: parts for Collage
      Process: 5x7 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 28)
      Description: "Boys "
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Gym Shorts Oval
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Broken Ovals
    - Title: Wrapper (Box 7, Folder 29)
      Description: Sit Ups
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Dalmation
      Process: 11x14 Dye Bleach Transfer
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Figure from "Desire" series
      Process: 8x10 Dye Bleach Transfer
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 30)
      Description: Figure negative block head
    - Title: Rock and column (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Process: 7x14 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Description: Figure red X
      Process: 16x20 Cibachrome
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Description: Figure X
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Sanctity
      Process: 11x17 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Statue
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 32)
      Description: Faith dinosaur
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Description: Four stars
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Title: pas une artiste (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 33)
      Description: Condom Figure globe
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Description: Figure for Guitar
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 34)
      Description: Saluki cut out
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: Experiment for Torso
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: Similar to Pom Poms
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 35)
      Description: 1919
  - Subseries E: Portrait
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Description: Astor, Patti
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 36)
      Process: 16x20 Color C-Print
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Description: Cutrone, Ronnie
    - Title:, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 37)
      Description: Eno, Brian
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Description: Mitchel, Eric
    - Title: (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Title:, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      Description: Ono, Yoko
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Description: Acconci, Vito
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 39)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Description: Bourdon, David
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
      Description: Byrne, David
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
      Description: Countess
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
      Description: Curtis, Jackie
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Description: Delight, Duca
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
      Description: "Gi Gi"
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Description: Hannah, Duncan
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 44)
      Description: Harrison, Jerry
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Description: Loud, Lance
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 45)
      Description: Hell, Richard
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 46)
      Description: Mr. Peanut
    - Title: (Box 8, Folder 47)
      Description: Mumps
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Description: Paik, Nam June
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 48)
      Description: Rivers, Larry
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 49)
      Description: "Ron" also labeled Sebastian
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
      Description: Sellers, Terence
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 51)
      Description: Smith, Jack
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 52)
      Description: Stefanotty, Robert and Maralee Johnson
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 53)
      Description: Talking Heads
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
      Description: White, James Chance
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Title: (Box 9, Folder 55)
      Description: Wilson, May
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Description: Unidentified Man
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Description: Unidentified man
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
      Description: Unidentified man -Hitler pose
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 58)
      Description: Unidentified Men
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Description: Tucker, Marcia
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 65)
      Description: Unidentified Woman
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
      Description: Nudeback, Gail
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Description: Unknown Woman
    - Title: (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Alessandra Gallery
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory, David Bourdon, and Hilton Kramer
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Battcock, Gregory, David Bourdon, Robert Steffanotty, Rosalind Krauss, Barbara Rose, Annette Michaelson, Hilton Kramer
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Brahms, Peter
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Burroughs, William, John Giorno, and Laurie Anderson
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Byron
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Churicova Inverse, Inna
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Coogan
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Cortez, Diego
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Dali, Salvador and Gregory Battcock
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy and Jimmy Jr
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Goodman, Ken
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Grief, Paula
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Harry, Debbie
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Hell, Richard - fragment
      Process: 4x8 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Idol, Billy
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Johnson, Ray
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: McCabe, Tom
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Nervous Breakdown
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Panfilov, Gleb
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Rosenblum, Robert and Jane Kaplowitz
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified subjects
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Saluki with unidentified subjects
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Smith, Patti - concert
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Smith, Rupert
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Teenage Jesus and the Jerks
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Varble, Stephen
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: "Victor Hugo"
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Warhol, Andy and "Victor Hugo"
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Winters, Robin
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Cropped portrait
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Hands
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified Band
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentfied Band
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified nude female subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified Subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
      Description: Unidentified subject
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
    - Title: (Box 11)
  - Subseries F: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Hats
      Number of Items: 31
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Giraffe
    - Title: (Box 12)
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Flamigo
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Ship
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Sink
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Joseph Kennedy House - Palm Beach
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: "Miami Florida" labeled on back by Laurie Simmons
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Street Scene
      Process: 6x7 Silver Gelatin
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Palm tree
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Two boys
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Umbrella
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Dark image, male nude?
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Painting Documentation
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Six headshots of a boy
    - Title: (Box 12)
      Description: Assorted male and female subjects, books
      Process: Polaroid
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: Tina Summerlin Photo
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: "Mario Monte - Star of Jack Smith's 'Normal Love'"
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 68)
      Description: Unidentitfied Subjects
      Process: 11x14 Color C-Print
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 70)
      Description: Ney Tait Fraser photograph
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 70)
      Description: Unknown photographer
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Description: Diego Cortez photo, Herman Dahled, Jon Rudd, Pierre Dahled, Winston Spriet, Brux
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      Description: Chris Stein photograph, Iggy Pop and Debbie Harry
    - Title:, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 71)
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 72)
      Description: Roberta Bayley photograph, Jimmy de Sana, Diego Cortez, and Anya Phillips
    - Title: (Box 13, Folder 72)
      Description: Lizbeth Mariano photograph
  - Subseries G: Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 14)
      Description: Paintings, sculptures, drawings and gallery interiors
      Number of Items: 58
    - Title: (Box 15)
      Description: Paintings, drawings, sculptures and gallery interiors
      Number of Items: 55
    - Title: (Box 16)
      Number of Items: 44
- Series IX: Half-tone triplicate reproductions by project
  - Subseries A: Salvation
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 99)
      Description: Household Protective Object
      Process: Half-tone
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 100)
      Description: Mask
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 101)
      Description: Powder
    - Title: (Box 60, Folder 102)
      Description: Blowfish
- Series X: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by project
  - Subseries A: 101 Nudes
    - Title: (Box 61)
      Description: 101 Nudes Contact Sheets
      Process: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheet
      Number of Items: 13
  - Subseries B: Submission
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 61)
      Description: Submission Contact Sheets
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 62)
      Number of Items: 43
    - Title:, 1978-1979 (Box 63)
      Number of Items: 16
  - Subseries C: Early Sex
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Mirror Beachball
  - Subseries D: $bfat
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Bubble Gum
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Pants, dog
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: With Jimmy Jr. on Beach
  - Subseries E: $dobjects
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Balloons
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Collage variations Popcorn "
    - Title: (Box 64)
  - Subseries F: Auto-Portrait
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Aluminum Foil
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Birds, Cardboard
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cap
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cellophane Tape
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Play Money
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Scar
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Slinkies
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Tape
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "With Jimmy Jr. Smoke Cowboy"
  - Subseries G: Cut Up
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cut Piece: Pendant and various Rupert Smith
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Cut Piece
  - Subseries H: Salvation
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Cap oval scratch Collage Parka, Condom, Powder, Playmoney"
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations
      Number of Items: 9
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Guitar
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Gym Shorts
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Collage variations including Letter O
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Various Powder
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: "Young boys Faith in the Cosmos"
- Series XI: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheets by theme
  - Subseries A: Events
    - Title: (Box 64)
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Anya Phillips, James Chance White
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Art
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Art Exhibition Space
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Atlana
      Number of Items: 6
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Diego Cortez
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Drag Queen
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Drag Queens
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Jackie Curtis
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Museum of Broadcasting
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Man with Monitor
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Nam June Paik
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Puerto Rican demonstration
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Sol le Witt Opening
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Street Fair
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Thom Cote, Anya Phillips
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Thom Cote, Richard Hell
    - Title: (Box 64)
      Description: Unidentified Events
  - Subseries B: Landscape
    - Title:, 1978 (Box 65)
      Description: Landscape series
  - Subseries C: Miscellaneous
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Auto Art cake
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: "Darrell Bagley Jimmy de Sana"
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Dog from Submission
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Dummy on Ceiling
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Jimmy Jr.
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Motorcycles
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Walk up Apartment and Loft
  - Subseries D: Portrait
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Acker, Kathy
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Anger, Kenneth
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Arrest
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Bagley, Darrell
    - Title:, 1988 (Box 65)
      Description: Bomb Magazine Staff photographed for Vanity Fair
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Brockis, Victor
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Churicova, Inna and Gleb Panfilov
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 65)
      Description: Clarence / Greenwich
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Cote, Thom
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Crutchfield, Robin
    - Title: (Box 65)
      Description: Cutrone, Ron (labeled on Negatives by JDS "Sebastian"nie
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: de Sana, Jimmy; Laurie Simmons
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: de Sana, Jo
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Dead Boys
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Delilght, Duca
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: GiGi
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Harry, Debra
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Hidalgo, Eddie
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Hidalgo, Eddie Christmas
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Lounge Lizards
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Mars and Teenage Head
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: McCormick, Carlo and Tessa Hughes-Freeland
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Mcdermitt, David and David McGuff, Laurie Simmons, Darrell Bagely, and Jimmy de Sana
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Nervous Breakdown; Voidoids
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Nylon, Judy; Jimmy de Sana, Thom Cote
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Phillips, Anya; James Chance White
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Poe, Amos
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Ramos, Jose, also labeled Victor Hugo (Halston's boyfriend)
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Resnick, Marcia
    - Title: (Box 66)
      Description: Ron (labeled on Negatives by JDS "Sebastian"
    - Title: (Box 66)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Sellers, Terence and Duncan Hannah
      Number of Items: 7
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Simmons, Laurie
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Smith, Patti
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Smith, Patti Eric and Robin Lee,
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Stefanotty, Robert
      Process: Silver Gelatin Contact Sheet Fragment
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Sussler, Betsy
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Talking Heads, Unidentified Band
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Teenage Head
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Warhol, Andy; Robert Stefanotty
    - Title: (Box 67)
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: White, James Chance and Lydia Lunch
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Unknown Band
    - Title: (Box 67)
      Description: Unidentified Subjects
      Number of Items: 14
    - Title: (Box 68)
      Number of Items: 36
  - Subseries E: Reproductions of Other Artists' Work
    - Title: (Box 68)
      Description: Other Artists' Work
  - Subseries F: Travel
    - Title: (Box 68)
      Description: Travel
      Number of Items: 11
- Series XII: Pat Hearn Materials
  Clippings, papers and color transparency slides collected by the Pat Hearn Gallery. The clippings are organized by date; when the date is unknown the documents are placed at the end of the subseries.
  - Subseries A: Color Transparency Slides
    - Title: (Box 69)
      Description: Documentation of work, ordered as found 1983 - 87 desending
      Process: Color Transparency Slides
      Number of Items: 470
    - Title: (Box 70)
      Description: Documentation of work, ordered as found 1979 -82 desending
      Number of Items: 565
    - Title: (Box 71)
      Description: Installation shots, 101 Nudes, Submission documentation, ordered as found
      Number of Items: 308
  - Subseries B: Papers and clippings organized by Pat Hearn Gallery
    - Title:, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 103)
      General note
      Flash Art review - February 1980
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 104)
      Roberta Smith review, Art in America - January 1981
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 105)
      New Figuration in America, New Directions Catalogue - 1981
    - Title:, 1981 (Box 72, Folder 106)
      New Voices, "6 Photographers" - 1981
    - Title:, 1985 (Box 72, Folder 107)
      "Big Car Show" catalogue - May 1985
    - Title:, 1986 (Box 72, Folder 108)
      Wolkenkratzer Art Journal, Diego Cortez/ de Sana interview - Oct 1986
    - Title:, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 109)
      Village Voice review - 24 February 1987
    - Title:, 1988 (Box 72, Folder 110)
      108 Review - January 1988
      NY Times review - 29 January 1988
      Art in America review - November 1988
    - Title:, 1989 (Box 72, Folder 111)
      "Mirroring Enigmas," essay by G. Roger Denison, Arts Magazine - May 1989
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 112)
      Journal of Contemporary Art, Laurie Simmons on Jimmy de Sana - Summer 1990
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 113)
      Jimmy de Sana obituary, Art World - September 1990
    - Title:, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 114)
      Two Arts Festival of Atlanta reviews - September 1990
    - Title:, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 115)
      NY Times Review, 101 Nudes - 4 January 1991
    - Title:, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 116)
      Print Collector's Newsletter, containing "Grotesque Photography," by Brooks Adams - January 1991
    - Title:, 1992, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 117)
      The Sexual Self review - October 1992
      Press Release PHG - September 1995
    - Title:, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 118)
      NY Times Review - 29 September 1995
    - Title:, 1995 (Box 72, Folder 119)
      Artforum review - November 1995
    - Title:, 1998 (Box 72, Folder 120)
      Art Resources Transfer Correspondence with Pat Hearn Gallery - November 1998
    - Title:, 2000 (Box 72, Folder 121)
      Press release and New York Times review, Bob Nickas 'D' at Sandrea Gering - March 2000
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 122)
      Art in America review - date unknown
      American Photographer review - date unknown
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 123)
      de Sana resume on Pat Hearn Letterhead
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 124)
      de Sana resumes on Pat Hearn Letterhead
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 125)
      PHG letterhead
- Series XIII: Ephemera
  Papers and clippings collected by the Jimmy De Sana estate. In subseries A, materials are arranged alphabetically by folder description. In subseries B, materials are retained in the original order given by Jimmy De Sana. There is one oversize item from this subseries, a record sleeve for James White and the Blacks, stored in box 78. It originally came last in Jimmy De Sana's sequence of ephemera.
  - Subseries A: Papers and clippings found throughout the Jimmy De Sana estate
    - Title:, 1996 (Box 72, Folder 126)
      Description: American Foundation for AIDS research flyer, AIDS quilt photo
      Number of Items:
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 127)
      Description: Birthday Card made by Janet Stein, unknown addressee
    - Title:, 1988, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 128)
      Description: Book of Nine, Gary Stephan - two small publications - Quotations from JDS
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 129)
      Description: Candid photos, Kenny Goodman
    - Title: (Box 72, Folder 130)
      Description: Colored Gels